That's good, you said you could untie your left hand.
良 かったね、左手ほどいてくれるって
Isn't it a little easier to do?
ちょっとやりやすいでしょ?
Isn't it easy to do?
やりやすいでしょ?
It's okay to take it slow.
ゆっくりでいいよ
Were you nervous?
緊張した?
I was nervous.
緊張した
緊 張 したね
But now you can do it.
だ けど、できるようになったね
That's a blowjob.
それがフェラチオだよ
Remember it.
覚えてきな
how was it?
どうだった?
Can I dry it here for a moment?
ちょっとここで一回乾燥していい?
Dry.
乾燥
how was it?
どうだった?
What does penis taste like?
おちんちんの味とは?
Strange taste.
不思議な味
Strange taste?
不思議な味?
A mysterious taste.
不 思議な味
The spicy taste is probably Meteor.
辛そうな味はメテオか
a little
ちょっとお
Hello, I want to bury my face in this.
ち さんさ、この中にさ、顔をうずくめたいんだけどさ
I don't like it.
嫌だな
Hey, just a little more.
ちょ、もうちょっと
Just a little more.
もうちょっと
Dry.
乾燥する
wise.
賢い
That's great.
偉いよ
Just a little more.
もうちょっと
My penis is starting to hurt a bit.
ちょっとおちんこ痛がなってきちゃった
Rubber?
ゴム?
You don't need it, right?
要らないでしょ?
Rubber.
ゴ ム
I haven't put it on from my hands, so I want some rubber from here as well.
手から付けてないから、ここからもゴム欲しい
You didn't put it on by hand, right?
手から付けてないでしょ?
where?
どこ?
It's okay from here.
ここからもいいじゃん
Isn't it good?
いいでしょ?
From outside.
外から
I said, ``I'm going out.''
外 出 すから、言った
It's okay, I'm going out.
外出すから、大丈夫
I'm going out, so it's okay, right?
外出すから、大丈夫でしょ?
I don't like it.
嫌だね
Because I'm going out.
外出しちゃうから
It's okay, it's okay.
大丈夫、大丈夫
Because I'm going out.
外出すから
It was okay until the beginning, right?
先駆まで大丈夫だったでしょ?
It's in.
入っちゃったね
It's not even half full yet.
まだ半分も入ってない
So, about half of this.
じゃあ、この半分ちょっと
Sorry, I'm leaving.
行っちゃうから、ごめんね
It's a bit impossible.
ちょっと無理だわ
Because it has to stop.
止まらないといけないから
Oh, I flushed it.
あ、流した
Sorry.
ごめんね
Please forgive me for a moment.
ちょっと許して
bitter?
苦い?
bitter.
苦い
Is it bitter?
苦 い か
tired.
疲れた
I'm tired.
疲れたね
Good luck!
がんばってね
See you soon, Kayuki-chan.
かゆきちゃん、またね
Thank you.
ありがとうね
bye bye.
バイバイ